Where Anything Goes and Everyone Belongs.
Jimmy's Hall is a history, drama film directed by Ken Loach.
Jimmy Gralton returns from New York and reopens his beloved community
hall, only to meet opposition from the local parish.
James Gralton, played by Barry Ward.
Oonagh, played by Simone Kirby.
Father Sheridan, played by Jim Norton.
Father Seamus, played by Andrew Scott.
Commander O'Keefe, played by Brían F. O'Byrne.
Mossie, played by Francis Magee.
Jimmy's Hall is a 2014 drama film directed by Ken Loach.
The film tells the story of the deportation to the United States in 1933 of Irish Communist Jimmy Gralton, who led
the Revolutionary Workers' Group, a precursor of the Communist Party of Ireland, in County Leitrim.
It stars Irish actor Barry Ward, along with Simone
Kirby, Jim Norton and Denise Gough.
The title refers to a rural dance hall built by
Gralton in his home town Effrinagh.
It was selected to compete for the Palme d'Or in the main
competition section at the 2014 Cannes Film Festival.
The film explores themes of poverty, ireland, 1930s.
The tone is emotional.